

## PEDRO SASTRE

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of birth: 19/10/95 Nationality: Argentina Telephone: +34 645222050

E-Mail: pedro2000sastre@gmail.com Address: Distrito Centro, Málaga

Web portfolio: www.pedro-sastre-2023.web.app

 ${\tt LinkedIn:} \ \underline{www.linkedin.com/in/pedro-sastre}$ 

GitHub: github.com/psastre

#### **PROFILE**

Data analyst specialized in marketing, trained to inform effective business strategies and decisions, with experience in small businesses where I incorporated best practices such as direct and personal communication, adaptability and flexibility for a dynamic environment, and the ability to engage in a variety of different types of tasks and projects.

## SKILLS AND LANGUAGES

-SQL -MySQL -Python -SQL Server

-Python -SQL S -Tableau -PHP

-Power BI -HTML -Excel -CSS

-Google Sheet -Javascript

- Azure - Spanish: C2 Native

-Matplotlib -English: C1 -Pandas -Portuguese: B1

-Numpy

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Sr. Data Analyst

Soluciones Hogar | 2022 - 2024 Intermediary between professionals and clients in home repair services.

-I led the market research and customer relationship analysis to implement a new internal software, web platform, and modernize communication channels. I focused on operational optimization and enhancing customer experience, particularly in email marketing. I supervised data collection, processing, and analysis for strategic insights. I collaborated with interdisciplinary teams and utilized tools such as Excel, SQL, Tableau, Python, and Azure for detailed analysis and report presentation.

# Database administrator and backend developer for Startup

ScoutPro | january 2023 -december 2023

- Responsible for designing, implementing, maintaining, and managing databases to ensure efficiency and security. Tasks include planning database design with various types of relationships, optimizing performance, and implementing security measures. The main tools used are SQL (MySQL and Workbench) and PHP.

## **Marketing Data Analyst**

Soluciones Hogar | 2020 - 2022 Intermediary between professionals and clients in home repair services.

-Responsible for collecting, cleaning, processing, exploring, analyzing, and communicating data related to email marketing campaigns and subscribers, as well as monthly statistics on order management and logistics. Additionally, provided assistance in utilizing best practices and communication with graphics in the finance area. Used tools such as Excel, Google Sheets, Tableau, SQL, and Python.

#### **ACADEMIC TRAINING**

#### **Google Data Analytics Certificate**

November 2023 - December 2023

## Alex the analyst bootcamp

Jenuary 2023 - July 2023

## **React bootcamp**

january 2021 - february 2021 | Scrimba Academy

## **Full Stack Dev. Bootcamp**

February 2018 - July 2018 | Digital House

### **Degree in Advertising**

2015 - 2019 | UADE